thenerdmag.com 2019-04-15

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is reviewed and revised from time to time. Your use of this site, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

 **1\. Log Files**

We at TheNerdMag use log files like many other websites. The information in the log files include:

  * Internet Protocol addresses (IP)
  * Types of browser
  * Internet Service Provider (ISP)
  * Date and time stamp
  * Referring and exit pages
  * Number of clicks

All of this information is not linked to anything that is personally identifiable.

 **2\. Cookies**

We use cookies to store information about visitor preferences and to record user-specific information on visits and pages the user views so as to provide a custom experience. In regard to third-party advertisers, TheNerdMag has no access or control over these cookies. You should review the respective privacy policies on any and all third-party ad servers for more information regarding their practices and how to opt-out.

If you wish to disable cookies you may do so through your web browser options. Instructions for doing so and for other cookie-related management can be found on the specific web browsers’ websites.

 _DoubleClick DART Cookie_

Google, a third party vendor, uses the DART cookie to serve ads on TheNerdMag. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting [Google’s Content Network Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

 _Amazon Affiliates Cookie_

Amazon Affiliates, a third party system, uses cookies to serve advertisements and links to products on Amazon.com.  You may read more about Amazon Affiliates and their [Operating Agreement here](https://affiliate-program.amazon.com/gp/associates/agreement?ie=UTF8&pf_rd_t=501&ref_=amb_link_84018271_6&pf_rd_m=ATVPDKIKX0DER&pf_rd_p=&pf_rd_s=assoc-right-1&pf_rd_r=&pf_rd_i=assoc_join_menu).

 _BuySellAds Cookie_

BuySellAds is an ad-serving platform and network that provide direct advertising opportunities for businesses and organizations. You may read more about this cookie and their [Privacy Policy here](http://buysellads.com/about/privacy).

DISQUS Comments

TheNerdMag uses Disqus Comments system to collect and manage comments on the blog. Disqus, as a third party service provider uses cookies to maintain your Disqus profile. You may easily opt out of the process by not posting a comment on the site.

 **3\. Other**

Users might be asked to subscribe to our newsletter by providing name and email address to receive communication from TheNerdMag. We use a secure op-in subscription system and we reserve the right to contact subscribers with information related to this website and blog. Subscribers may unsubscribe anytime and every email delivered will contain an “Unsubscribe” link.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at admin@thenerdmag.com .

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

## External Sites

TheNerdMag  may often link to content on external websites. The Site has no control over the nature of content on these external websites or their policies regarding information and privacy. For further information, please review the individual policies of these websites.

Last Updated:  May 23, 2014
